Art Buchwald Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Oversize, 1925-2007 (Box OV 1-OV 18)
  - Personal
    - Prosthetic leg worn by Buchwald, 2006 (Container 213, Prosthetic leg) (Box OV 12)
    - Paris years
      - Poster and manifesto created by the Bull Moose Party calling for the repeal of the 19th Amendment, 1952, 1959 (Container 215, Bull Moose Party) (Box OV 7)
      - Program for the opera Carmen, 1960, Mar. 25 (Container 217, Printed ephemera) (Box OV 7)
      - Restaurant menus for Chinese Rathskeller, Lapérouse, Lamère Catherine, Le Sanglier Bleu, and Maxim’s, 1953-1959 (Container 218, Restaurant menus) (Box OV 7)
      - Posters commemorating the Running of the Bulls in Pamplona, Spain, 1958 (Container 218, Running of the bulls) (Box OV 7)
    - Front page mockup of a Los Angeles Times issue featuring photographs of Buchwald and wishing him a happy 60th birthday, 1985, Oct. 20 (Container 218, 60th birthday) (Box OV 11)
    - United States Marine Corps
      - Buchwald’s enlistment photograph inscribed by Robert E. Cushman, Commandant, circa 1972 (Container 219, Photographs) (Box OV 7)
      - Service ribbons, medical and toiletry items from a soldier's first aid kit, circa 1942-1947 (Container 219, Service ribbons and first aid kit items) (Box OV 5)
Appendix A: Partial list of Significant Correspondents in the VIP Chronological File
The list below highlights some of the significant correspondents represented in the VIP Chronological grouping of the General Correspondence series. The below is not a comprehensive list of all names found in the grouping.
Alsop, Joseph
Alsop, Stewart
Brinkley, David
Brown, Helen Gurley
Caen, Herb
Carpenter, Liz
Chancellor, John
Condon, Richard
Cronkite, Walter
Donaldson, Sam
Evans, Kay
Evans, Roland
Forbes, Malcolm
Galbraith, John Kenneth
Glenn, John
Greenfield, Meg
Guggenheim, Charles
Harriman, Pamela Digby Churchill Hayward
Harriman, W. Averell
Hellman, Lillian
Hoppe, Arthur Watterson
Lewis, Anthony
Lindsay, John
Marcus, Stanley
McGrory, Mary
Pearson, Drew
Rather, Dan
Rozelle, Pete
Safire, William
Sawyer, Diane
Schlatter, George
Schuller, Robert H.
Simon, William E.
Smith, Liz
Stevens, Roger L.
Stone, Sharon
Valenti, Jack
Vonnegut, Kurt
Wald, Richard C.
Wallace, Irving
Walters, Barbara
Wasserman, Lew
Will, George F.
Wouk, Herman
Appendix B: Partial Disk Inventory
Attached is a searchable PDF copy of an inventory created by Buchwald or an assistant of some of his word-processing disks. The inventory lists file names across fifteen disks and classifies files as "column," "speech," or "letter." Date spans are not indicated on the inventory. The digital ID for each disk is noted in brackets on the inventory.